Local 1199 Records 5510
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Records
1956-1973
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU)
RWDSU Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union
5510
55 cubic feet
55 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection includes meeting minutes, financial records, membership records, collective bargaining files, for the Hospital Division of Local 1199.
5658202
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
CB, January 13, 2006
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 14, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5206: Local 1199 Records 5206-D: Local 1199 Drug Division Records 5206-G: Local 1199 Guild Division Records 5206-PR: Local 1199 President Leon Davis Records 5206-S: Local 1199 Executive Secretary Moe Foner Records 5206-X: Local 1199 Clippings and News Releases 5457: Mark Lillian Collection of Roosevelt Hospital (NYC) vs. Local 1199, 1962 Representational Dispute Documents 5520m: "Building a Union in the Hospitals: the Organization of Local 1199 at Montefoire Hospital, 1948-1958" Manuscript 5525: Local 1199 Additional Files 5651: Local 1199 Additional Records 5768: Sidney Cahn Collection of League of Voluntary Hospitals & Homes of New York vs. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union Arbitration Files 5680 OH: Local 1199 Oral History Project 5854: Local 1199 Additional Records 5871: Local 1199 Additional Records 5929: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Records 5929 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 5929 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 5929 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 5933: Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union News files 5933 P: Local 1199 Photograph Files 5938: Local 1199 Leon Davis Additional Papers 5945: Local 1199 Additional Records 5948: Local 1199 (Rochester, N.Y.) Records 5984 AV: Local 1199 Additional Videos 5984 AV: Local 1199 Additional Videos 6016: Local 1199 National Benefit and Pension Fund Records 6062: Paul Friedman Collection of National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199 Miscellany 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6084 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings 6140 P: Local 1199 Moe Foner Photographs 6169: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files 6169 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 6169 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 6169: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files
Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union (New York, N.Y.)
5658202
- Hospital Division Council [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Hospital Division Council [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Hospital Division Council [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Hospital Division Council [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- General Membership [folder 1 of 2], 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- General Membership [folder 2 of 2], 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Hospital Leadership, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Hospital Staff [folder 1 of 2], 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Hospital Staff [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hospital Team, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Analysis Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Monthly Dues Reports, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bronx [folder 1 of 4], 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Bronx [folder 2 of 4], 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Bronx [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Bronx [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Bronx [folder 1 of 5], 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Bronx [folder 2 of 5], 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Bronx [folder 3 of 5], 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Bronx [folder 4 of 5], 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Bronx [folder 5 of 5], 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn [folder 1 of 6], 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn [folder 2 of 6], 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn [folder 3 of 6], 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn [folder 4 of 6], 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn [folder 5 of 6], 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn [folder 6 of 6], 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn [folder 1 of 5], 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn [folder 2 of 5], 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn [folder 3 of 5], 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn [folder 4 of 5], 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn [folder 5 of 5], 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Connecticut [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Connecticut [folder 2 of 2], 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Downtown [folder 1 of 3], 1964-1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Downtown [folder 2 of 3], 1964-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Downtown [folder 3 of 3], 1964-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Downtown [folder 1 of 5], 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Downtown [folder 2 of 5], 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Downtown [folder 3 of 5], 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Downtown [folder 4 of 5], 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Downtown [folder 5 of 5], 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- New Jersey [folder 1 of 7], 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- New Jersey [folder 2 of 7], 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- New Jersey [folder 3 of 7], 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- New Jersey [folder 4 of 7], 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- New Jersey [folder 5 of 7], 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- New Jersey [folder 6 of 7], 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- New Jersey [folder 7 of 7], 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- New Jersey [folder 1 of 5], 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- New Jersey [folder 2 of 5], 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- New Jersey [folder 3 of 5], 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- New Jersey [folder 4 of 5], 1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- New Jersey [folder 5 of 5], 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 1 of 5], 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 2 of 5], 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 3 of 5], 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 4 of 5], 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 5 of 5], 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 1 of 6], 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 2 of 6], 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 3 of 6], 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 4 of 6], 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 5 of 6], 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Queens-Long Island [folder 6 of 6], 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Uptown [folder 1 of 10], 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Uptown [folder 2 of 10], 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Uptown [folder 3 of 10], 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Uptown [folder 4 of 10], 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Uptown [folder 5 of 10], 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Uptown [folder 6 of 10], 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Uptown [folder 7 of 10], 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Uptown [folder 8 of 10], 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Uptown [folder 9 of 10], 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Uptown [folder 10 of 10], 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Uptown [folder 1 of 4], 1972 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Uptown [folder 2 of 4], 1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Uptown [folder 3 of 4], 1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Uptown [folder 4 of 4], 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Abbet Manor Nursing Home, 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Adelphi Hospital, 1964-1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Albert Einstein Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1964-1972 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Albert Einstein Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1964-1972 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Albert Einstein Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1964-1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Alps Manor Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Alps Manor Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Alps Manor Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1972 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Associated Residence for Women, 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Association Respected Females, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Atlantic City Hospital, 1964-1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Barnert Memorial Hospital, 1964-1968 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Barry Industries, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Bayonne Hospital, 1964-1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Bayshore Nursing Home, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Beekman-Downtown Hospital, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Bel Air Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Bel Air Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Berkeley Hall Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Berkeley Hall Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1972 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Beth Abraham Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Beth Abraham Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Beth Abraham Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Beth Abraham Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Beth Israel Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Beth Israel Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Beth Israel Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Beth Israel Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Birchwood Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Birchwood Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Birchwood Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Bloomfield Convalescent Home, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Bloomfield Window Cleaners, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Blue Hills Convalescent Home, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Booth Memorial Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Booth Memorial Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1971 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Brandywine Nursing Home, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Bronx Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1966 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Bronx Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1966 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Bronx Eye Infirmary [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Bronx Eye Infirmary [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Bronx Hebrew Home and Hospital, 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Bronx-Lebanon Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Bronx-Lebanon Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Bronx-Lebanon Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Bronx-Lebanon Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Bronx Municipal Hospital Center, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Brookdale Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1956-1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Brookdale Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1956-1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Brookdale Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1956-1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Brookdale Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1956-1971 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Brooklyn Eye & Ear Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Brooklyn Eye & Ear Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Brooklyn Eye & Ear Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Brooklyn Hebrew Home and Hospital, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1963-1968 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1963-1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1963-1968 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn Jewish Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Jewish Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Jewish Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1972 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Brooklyn Jewish-Greenpoint Hospital, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Brookside Nursing Home, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Brookwood Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Brookwood Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Brookwood Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Brunswick Park Nursing Home [folder 1 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Brunswick Park Nursing Home [folder 2 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Brunswick Park Nursing Home [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Brunswick Park Nursing Home [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Buckley Home, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Burke Rehabilitation Center, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Caledonian Hospital, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Cardiac Center, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Carson C. Peck Memorial Hospital, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Cedar Manor [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Cedar Manor [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Central General Hospital, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Centre Manor Nursing Home, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Cherry Nursing Home, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Christ Hospital, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Clara Maas Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Clara Maas Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Clara Maas Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Clara Maas Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Clinton Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1971 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Clinton Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1971 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Colchester Home, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Columbia University [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Columbia University [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Columbus Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1963-1969 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Columbus Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1963-1969 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Columbus Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1963-1969 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Community Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1965-1971 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Community Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1965-1971 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Community Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1965-1971 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Community Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1965-1971 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Cornell Hall Nursing Home, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Crown Heights Hospital, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Daughters of Israel [folder 1 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Daughters of Israel [folder 2 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Daughters of Israel [folder 3 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Daughters of Israel [folder 4 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Daughters of Israel [folder 5 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Daughters of Jacob [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Daughters of Jacob [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Daughters of Jacob [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Daughters of Jacob [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Daughters of Miriam [folder 1 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Daughters of Miriam [folder 2 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Daughters of Miriam [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Daughters of Miriam [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Davis Nursing Home, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Deepdale Hospital, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Dr. Friedman Nursing Home, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Doctor's Hospital, 1962-1966 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Donnelly Hospital, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Dumont Hospital, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- East 91st Street Hospital, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- East Orange General Hospital, 1964-1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Eden Park, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Einstein Medical College, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Elizabeth General, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Elizabeth Manor Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Elizabeth Manor Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Elizabeth Manor Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Elizabeth Manor Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Elmhurst Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Elmhurst Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Elmwood Manor Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Elmwood Manor Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Elmwood Manor Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Englewood Hospital, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Evangelical Deaconess Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Evangelical Deaconess Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Fitkin Memorial Hospital, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Flower-Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 1 of 6], 1959-1971 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Flower-Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 2 of 6], 1959-1971 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Flower-Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 3 of 6], 1959-1971 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Flower-Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 4 of 6], 1959-1971 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Flower-Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 5 of 6], 1959-1971 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Flower-Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 6 of 6], 1959-1971 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Flushing Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Flushing Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Flushing Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Flushing Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Forest Manor Nursing Home, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Freeport Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Freeport Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Freeport Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Freeport Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- French Hospital [folder 1 of 6], 1962-1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- French Hospital [folder 2 of 6], 1962-1971 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- French Hospital [folder 3 of 6], 1962-1971 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- French Hospital [folder 4 of 6], 1962-1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- French Hospital [folder 5 of 6], 1962-1971 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- French Hospital [folder 6 of 6], 1962-1971 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Garden Terrace Nursing Home, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Garret Food, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Glenside Nursing Home, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Golden Heights Nursing Home, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Golden Manor Nursing Home, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Gouverneur Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Gouverneur Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Gouverneur Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Gouverneur Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Gracie Square Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Gracie Square Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Gracie Square Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Gracie Square Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Graham Nursing Home, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Grand Central Hospital, 1959-1963 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Green Hill Nursing Home, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Greenspan, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Hamilton Pavilion Nursing Homes, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Harlem Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1960-1968 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Harlem Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1960-1968 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Harlem Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1960-1968 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Harlem Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1960-1968 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Hartford Convalescent Home [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Hartford Convalescent Home [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Haym Solomon Home [folder 1 of 4], 1961-1971 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Haym Solomon Home [folder 2 of 4], 1961-1971 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Haym Solomon Home [folder 3 of 4], 1961-1971 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Haym Solomon Home [folder 4 of 4], 1961-1971 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Hebrew Home and Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Hebrew Home and Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Hebrew Home and Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Hebrew Home and Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Helene Fuld Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Helene Fuld Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Helene Fuld Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Hempstead General Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Hempstead General Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Hempstead General Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Hempstead General Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- High Ridge Nursing Home, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Hilaire Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Hilaire Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Hilaire Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Hillside Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Hillside Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1971 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Holy Comforter Hospital, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Home of the Sages, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Home of Old Israel, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Horn and Hardart [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1968 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Horn and Hardart [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1968 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Hospital for Joint Diseases [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1971 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Hospital for Joint Diseases [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1971 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- House of the Holy Comforter [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- House of the Holy Comforter [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- House of the Holy Comforter [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Hughes Convalescent Home, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Huntington Nursing Home, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Institute of Physical and Medical Rehabilitation, 1959-1964 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Irvington Nursing Home [folder 1 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Irvington Nursing Home [folder 2 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Irvington Nursing Home [folder 3 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Irvington Nursing Home [folder 4 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Italian Hospital, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Jacques Lowe Community Hospital, 1962-1964 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Jamaica Hospital, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Jersey City Medical Center [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Jersey City Medical Center [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Jewish Brooklyn Hospital, 1959-1964 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Jewish Chronic Diseases Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1968 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Jewish Chronic Diseases Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1960-1968 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Jewish Chronic Diseases Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1960-1968 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Jewish Home and Hospital [folder 1 of 8], 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Jewish Home and Hospital [folder 2 of 8], 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Jewish Home and Hospital [folder 3 of 8], 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Jewish Home and Hospital [folder 4 of 8], 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Jewish Home and Hospital [folder 5 of 8], 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Jewish Home and Hospital [folder 6 of 8], 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Jewish Home and Hospital [folder 7 of 8], 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Jewish Home and Hospital [folder 8 of 8], 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Jewish Home and Rehabilitation Center, 1967-1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Jewish Hospital for Chronic Diseases, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Jewish Memorial Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 26, Folder 12)